// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the Capital of Punjab ?",
    answer: "Chandigarh",
    options: [
      "Ludhiana",
      "Jalandhar",
      "Chandigarh",
      "Moga"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many districts are there in the state ?",
    answer: "22",
    options: [
      "32",
      "22",
      "27",
      "28"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "How many Legislative Assembly seats are here ?",
    answer: "117",
    options: [
      "117",
      "121",
      "134",
      "75"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which is the largest city of Punjab ?",
    answer: "Ludhiana",
    options: [
      "Ludhiana",
      "Jalandhar",
      "Gurdaspur",
      "Patiala"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "CM of Punjab (2020)?",
    answer: "Capt Amarinder Singha",
    options: [
      "Capt Amarinder Singha",
      "Sr Parkask Singh Badal",
      "Bhagwant Mann",
      "Sukhbir Singh Badal" 
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many candidates does the state send to the Parliament ?",
    answer: "13",
    options: [
      "13",
      "14",
      "16",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the official language of the state ?",
    answer: "Punjabi",
    options: [
      "Punjabi",
      "Gurmukhi",
      "Hindi",
      "English"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the literacy rate of the state ?",
    answer: "76.68 %",
    options: [
      "88.2 %",
      "76.68 %",
      "81.98 %",
      "88.09 %"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the emblem of Punjab ?",
    answer: "Lion Capital of Ashoka",
    options: [
      "Khanda",
      "Lion Capital of Ashoka",
      "Eagle",
      "Tiger"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the state animal of Punjab ?",
    answer: "Black buck",
    options: [
      "Black buck",
      "Lion",
      "Tiger",
      "Eagle"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Punjab is located in ____",
    answer: "North - west",
    options: [
      "North - west",
      "North - east",
      "SOUTH- EAST",
      "SOUTH -WEST"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "._____ is the main occupation of the people of Punjab.",
    answer: "Agriculture",
    options: [
      "Fishing",
      "cattle rearing",
      "Agriculture",
      "Carpantery"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What crops are grown in Punjab?  ",
    answer: "all of the above",
    options: [
      "Wheat and rice",
      "Wheat ans rice",
      "Sugarcane",
      "all of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "In which year the current state of Punjab was created",
    answer: "1947",
    options: [
      "1960",
      "1947",
      "1947",
      "1972"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which one is the largest city in Punjab in area wise",
    answer: "Ludhiana",
    options: [
      "Ludhiana",
      "Amritsar",
      "Mohali",
      "Jalandhar"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "The Lohri festival is dedicated to this god.",
    answer: "The god of sun",
    options: [
      "The god of Harvest",
      "The god of moon.",
      "The god of sun",
      "The god of rain"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "When is Baisakhi celebrated?",
    answer: "13th April",
    options: [
      "1st April",
      "16th April",
      "13th April",
      "23rd April"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which of the dishes are belongs to special Punjabi cuisine",
    answer: "Rajma chawal",
    options: [
      "Kadhi chawal",
      "Rajma chawal",
      "RGurwala chawal",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Punjab is the major producer of?",
    answer: "wheat, rice and dairy products",
    options: [
      "corn, wheat and rice",
      "sugar, bajra and wheat",
      "soyabean, oats and barley",
      "wheat, rice and dairy products"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },

];